Curriculum vitae

Lucas Hilgevoord

Educations

Game/Media Development

Mediacollege Amsterdam 2017 – Present

VMBO (Graduated in 2016)

Spinoza Lyceum Amsterdam 2012 – 2016

Work experience

Jumbo AGF

Jumbo de Aker 2015 – 2019

Vrije Universiteit Internship

Amsterdam, Technical support 2019 – 2019

Skills

Languages

Dutch, native language Engels

Programming Languages

C/C++/C# Javascript HTML/CSS Swift

Program Knowledge

Adobe Photoshop Blender XCode Unity Unreal Git

Profile

My name is Lucas Hilgevoord,

A 19 years old student who studies Game Development at the MediaCollege in Amsterdam. I enjoy to immerse myself in the world of technologies such as VR, AR and Arduino/esp. To be able to be creative and create things from scratch, to whatever I can think of works great for me.

Personalia

Name: Lucas Hendrik Jacob Hilgevoord.

Address: Pyreneeën 51, 1060NP Amsterdam.

Date of birth: 09-05-2000.

Nationality: Dutch.

 Phone:
 06-23681712 / 020-6829897

 E-mail:
 <u>lucashilgevoord@hotmail.com</u>

Interests: Games, Reverse engineering, Robotics,

Piano, Guitar, Basketball.

Portfolio: https://lucashilgevoord.com

driver's license: AM, B